you is that if
individuals are earning money
now and they're
using Buy Pay Later
to buy things
online and then they're
it on not very
productive things It's not
like they're buying maybe
you buy a MacBook
and you do podcasts
on your MacBook and
you make money with
that that's great That's
productive spending It's like
la boos and it
nailed it So there's
a of like non
productive spending So I'll
use like a say
on TikTok shop right
So I spoke to
a lot of people
who are involved in
that ecosystem and saying
that okay what are
people buying And then
a of it are
not actually productive stuff
They're like perfumes or
they're like and so
there's just like stuff
you don't actually need
So they don't fully
make you they don't
influence your Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah The
ROI is not great
The ROI is not
great That is terrible
right It's Yeah it's
terrible right So what
has Buy Pay Later
done And what has
like what has credit
cards you done for
the S back then